Love is the greatest gift of all
Christmas Wedding Planner is a romance, family, tv
movie film directed by Justin G. Dyck.
Wedding Planner, Kelsey Wilson, is about to have her big break:
planning her beloved cousin's lavish and exclusive wedding.
Everything is going smoothly until Connor McClane, a devilishly handsome
private investigator, shows up and turns Kelsey's world upside-down.
Hired by a secret source, Connor quickly disrupts the upcoming
nuptials but wins Kelsey's heart in the process.
Kelsey, played by Jocelyn Hudon.
Connor, played by Stephen Huszar.
Aunt Olivia, played by Kelly Rutherford.
Emily, played by Rebecca Dalton.
Todd, played by Eric Hicks.
George, played by Joey Fatone.
Christmas Wedding Planner is a 2017 Canadian drama
romance film, directed by Justin G.
Dyck and screenplay by Keith Cooper.
The film is based on Once Upon A Wedding by Stacy Connelly.
The tone is emotional.